[
    {
        "question": "Mala",
        "answers": [
            "Die Tafel",
            "Der Tasche",
            "Die Tasche",
            "Die Taschen"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Caderno",
        "answers": [
            "Der Heft",
            "Das Heft",
            "Die Heft",
            "Die Heften"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Caneta",
        "answers": [
            "Der kulis",
            "Der kuli",
            "Die Tische",
            "Der Tische"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Borracha",
        "answers": [
            "Die Radiergummi",
            "Der Radiergummi",
            "Die Fenster",
            "Der kuli"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Mesa",
        "answers": [
            "Der Tisch",
            "Die Tischen",
            "Die Tafel",
            "Der Tischen"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Livro",
        "answers": [
            "Das Buch",
            "Die Buch",
            "Der Buch",
            "Die Büchen"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lapis",
        "answers": [
            "Der stuhe",
            "Die Bleistifte",
            "Das Bleistifte",
            "Der Bleistift"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Lixo",
        "answers": [
            "Die papierkorb",
            "Der stift",
            "Das papierkorb",
            "Der papierkorb"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Janela",
        "answers": [
            "Die fenster",
            "Der fenster",
            "Das fenster",
            "Die tabel"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quadro",
        "answers": [
            "Der Apfel",
            "Die Tafel",
            "Die Tafels",
            "Das Tafel"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Cadeira",
        "answers": [
            "Das stuhe",
            "Die stuhl",
            "Der stuhl",
            "Die stühen"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Agua",
        "answers": [
            "Die Flasche",
            "Der Flasche",
            "Das Flasche",
            "Der Flaschen"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jornal",
        "answers": [
            "jornal",
            "heft",
            "zeitung",
            "schalfen"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Chapeu",
        "answers": [
            "die Hut",
            "das Hut",
            "der Hut",
            "den Hut"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    }
]